Hawk.
霍克
Calm.
別動
Oh shit!
啊 媽的
God damn sons of bitches.
這群婊子養的
God shit me more.
這群廢物
- Hey you seen Coulter? - No.
- 嘿 看見庫爾特了嗎  - 沒有
Listen up! When them pelts is clean...
聽好了 你們把這些毛皮清理干淨以後
I want you to wrap 'em up real tight.
把它們包緊了
Remember, we're not doin' no 15 pelt bales...
記住 我們總共要包30捆
We're doin' 30 pelt bales.
不是15捆
Fitzgerald.
菲茨傑拉德
- Captain. - Where are we with the haul?
- 隊長 - 打獵情況如何
What are you thinking?
你覺得情況如何
Well...
恩
I'm thinkin' what ever it is that they're hunting out there...
不管他們打到了什麼動物
I'm hoping they don't need another shot.
他們最好別再開槍了
Let's make sure we're at ahead by dawn.
天亮前 我們必須動身
We've been done by this morning.
我們今早就准備好了
I don't like to be not here myself by now,but you know we're not.
我也不想現在還呆在這 但是你也知道我們還走不了
We men are to tired.
大家都已經很累了
I figure we're only few days out from the fort, we're trapped out.
我們距離營地只有幾天路程了 現在事情還沒辦完
All we have to worry about...
現在我們首要任務是
- Is getting some fresh meat for the boys. - Yeah.
- 給大家弄點新鮮的肉吃 - 恩
Yeah, you seen Coulter?
恩 你看見庫爾特了嗎
Hey, we took down an elk.
嘿 我們打到一頭麋鹿
A big one.
很大只
We're gonna need some help to haul the meat back.
幫忙一起去運回來吧
You let me know when it's on the spit.
等肉烤熟了
I'll help with it then.
再來叫我
Hey no, come on fellas, I need your help.
嘿 別這樣 我需要幫忙
we needed help when we were bustin'are asses loadin' them bales.
我們捆皮毛累得半死的時候 你又在哪
I've been out here so long eating this damn beaver meat...
吃了這麼久的海狸肉
I'm actually starting to miss my wifes cooking.
我都開始想念我老婆做的飯了
Shit, I'm actually startin'to miss your wife.
是嗎 我也很想她
Why don't you shut the hell?...
閉嘴
Help.
救命
Is that Coulter?
那是庫爾特嗎
- Stay together. - Jim, you go get the captain.
- 別亂跑 - 吉姆 去把隊長叫來
Jesus Christ!
上帝啊
- Shut up! - Help him!
- 閉嘴 - 快幫幫他
- Anybody seeing them? - Stay quiet dammit...
- 有人看見那群土著在哪嗎 - 別出聲 媽的
God damn.
該死
They got Thomas.
托馬斯在他們手上
I can't see 'em.
我看不到他們
- Get down. - Oh shit.
- 趴下 - 該死
They are everywhere.
到處都是他們的人
We are surrounded.
我們被包圍了
- They're everywhere. - Soho ...
- 到處都是他們的人 - 索何
Stay here.
別出去
No, no. Oh no!
不 不要 噢 不
- Stay down. - Help me!
- 趴下 - 救救我
They want us out in the open ...
他們想逼我們去空曠的地方
Someone get up the hill!
到山上打他們
Nobody move, just stay where you are.
大家呆在原地 別亂動
Well they want the pelts.
他們想要皮毛
We go and get on them 'bout right now ...
我們要是現在不去把皮毛拿過來
... or we gonna lose it all.
他們會把皮毛全部搶走
Get to the boat.To the boat, son.
上船 快上船 孩子
Move, move, move.
快點 快點 快點
Leave the forest,leave the forest ...
快離開樹林 快離開
... to the boat.
上船
Hawk!
霍克
Hawk, hawk!
霍克 霍克
Grab some pelts!
帶著皮毛
Come on, grab the pelt!
快點 帶著皮毛
Grab the pelt.
帶著皮毛
Come on.
快點
- Get this to my little girl. - You're coming with us I'm gettin' help ...
- 把這個給我女兒  - 我們不會扔下你的 我去找人來幫忙
Lean on me, just get ...
扶著我
Glass!
格拉斯
Get to the boat!
上船
You fuckin' son of a ...
你個狗娘養的
Get on the fuckin' boat.
快他媽上船
Help.
救命
Move, come on.
快走 快點
Come on.
快點
Cut the rope.
把繩子剪了
- Cut the rope. - Wait for Amos, wait for Amos...
- 把繩子剪了 - 等等阿摩司 等等阿摩司
We go now.
現在就走
Go to the cannon.
開大炮
Don't leave, please.
別走 求求你們了
And the dust becomes flower...
塵土幻變作花朵
Amen.
阿門
When the morning was clear...
當太陽升起
Amen.
阿門
Ready?
准備好了嗎
Hold still.
別動
Where did you learn that?
你這是從哪學的
My father was a doctor.
我父親曾經是個醫生
Bridger.
布裡傑
Captain we got a small tree niggers out here ...
隊長 樹林裡有頭小野獸
... waiting to finish the job.
在虎視眈眈著我們
- Hold there. - Yes.
- 按住這裡 - 好
Tell me you got some kind of plan.
告訴我 你已經想好對策了
Glass.
格拉斯
Missouri is no good.
密蘇裡河很危險
Not while the rees runnin' it.
是那群土著的領地
We got to get off this boat ...
我們得下船
Oh you want to get off the boat?
你要我們下船?
Then what we're gonna do, hah?
然後我們怎麼辦 哈
We're gonna take our furs...
難道我們就拿著皮毛
And sit out there amongst the ree,like a bunch of god damn ducks.
去樹林裡 等著土著們找上門來嗎
Only safe thing to do is track a new course
現在最安全的辦法是
...back upon land.
上岸找一條新的路線
We'll add weeks to the trip.
我們會需要多幾周時間
Better then floating back down there where they can get their eyes on us.
那也比回去等死要好
They got eyes on you right now, son.
在他們眼裡 我們早就死了
What I'm saying is we stay on the boat.
我是說 我們不要上岸
Try the course toward the fort ...
往我們的營地開
We take the chances on the water.
我們在水上求生
Glass knows this territory better than the rest of us put together.
格拉斯比我們都熟悉這塊地區
It's his job to get us home safe.
他的責任就是確保我們安全回去
- Get us home safe? - Yeah.
- 確保我們安全回去? - 恩
Need I remind you we already lost 32 men?
需要我提醒你 我們已經死了32個人了嗎
33 now.
現在是33個了
They were my men Fitzgerald,i know how many I lost.
他們是我手下的人 菲茨傑拉德 死了多少我自己清楚
We do like glass says,that's the end of it.
我們按格拉斯說的做 就這樣
We have to set the boat loose.
我們必須把船扔了
If ree are tracking us, they will find it down the river.
如果土著在追蹤我們的話 他們會在河堤附近找到我們的船
The best course is hike in on the ground and follow it down...
現在最好的辦法是
... to fort kahowa.
徒步走到凱何華營地
- What, on foot? - Are you sure?
- 什麼 徒步? - 你確定嗎
It'd be a week before we get there.
那至少得要一周
Unless we come across a poach straying prison horses.
除非我們遇到一群走散的監獄馬群
Ain't no poach that far over.
那麼遠哪會有什麼動物
Right, captain.
沒錯 隊長
Losing this boat is god damn stinking.
我們應該留著這艘船
Besides the rees ain't that stupid ...
再說了 土著也沒那麼傻
If we keep it, we can lay it up around hours peak.
我們應該把船留在山上
Quit acting like you know what you're talking about Fitzgerald.
別裝得好像你什麼都懂 菲茨格爾德
Ain't nobody talking to you.
我又沒和你說話
Who'd listen to you anyway.
誰會聽你的
God damn, can't even ...Find fuckin...Potato shit...
媽的 這裡連個土豆都找不到
All I'm sayin' is ...
我的意思是
... camp roollin is just up away ...
上面不遠處有一個營地
And we can hold up there.
我們可以在那裡歇歇
We walk.
別廢話了
Yeah, I'm sure we will.
我還能有什麼辦法
God damn, wish my daddy was a doctor then he could have bought me a captains job.
媽的 我爸怎麼不是醫生 這樣我也可以做隊長了
So what do we do now?
所以 現在我們該怎麼辦
...praying that poach ain't rockin'if we ever get back here...
祈禱我們會遇見
- ... to pick them up. - Make sure to mark this place.
- 迷路的馬群嗎 - 記住在這裡做記號
We're leaving a fortune under these rocks.
我們要把東西埋在石頭下面
No more room here, you gotta move up the hill.
這裡沒地方放了 你在上面找找看吧
- Glass. - Chart a course ...
- 格拉斯 - 找一條能夠
Try as you can figure to get us around the reef.
到達暗礁的路線
Yes sir.
好的
This ain't right, this ain't right.
這樣不對 這樣不對
We all know that this furs ain't won't be here by the time we come back.
我們都清楚 我們回來的時候這些皮毛肯定不會在了
There is no way we can hold them all the way back...
我們是不可能帶著它們
... to the fort.
回營地的
Not the way we're going, besides arikara is
我們要走的那條路很危險 而且這一帶附近都是阿裡卡拉人
...spread all through their territory,we want to go with our hands free.
所以我們最好空手上路
I'm tryin' to tell you're gonna lose this pelts.
我在告訴你 我們會失去這些皮毛
Would you rather hold on to the pelts or your life?
是皮毛重要還是命重要
Life?
命?
What life you talking about? I ain't got no life.
什麼命? 我哪有什麼命啊
I just got livin' the only way I get to do that is through this pelts.
我要想活命 還得靠這些皮毛呢
Fuck!
媽的
Calm there Fitz.
冷靜點 菲茨
Make a way, I'm going home ...
讓開點 我要回家了
After six months working my ass of like a mule,
六個月以來 我像頭騾子一樣累的要死要活的
risking my neck ...
冒著生命危險
... men dying and for what?
看著我的隊友死去 這一切都為了什麼
Damn nearly lost everything.
我幾乎失去了所有東西
This job's been fucked from the start.
這項任務一開始就有問題
There is the one being fuckin' us.
惹最多麻煩的人在這呢
Any of you boys wonder how ree managed to get their drop on us
你們難道不奇怪 土著人是怎麼找到我們的嗎
...for Mr. glass here,
格拉斯先生
was supposed to be looking out for that fucking thing.
的任務是放風
- All them Pawnee buddies of his. - Pawnees as much against rees as the rest of us.
- 他和他的那群波尼兄弟 - 波尼人和我們是站在同一戰線的
Yeah?
是嗎
What about his little...
那他這個
... half-breed son?
混血兒子呢
And what kind of savage you think his momma was.
誰知道他老娘是個什麼貨色
Lay of the boy Fitz.
別說了 菲茨
All I'm saying here.
我是說
Savage is savage ...
野蠻人 終究還是野蠻人
Hey glass.
嘿 格拉斯
Is it true what they say? That you shootin' a lieutenant ...
他們說的是真的嗎 你和那群野蠻人一起生活的時候
... while you was living with them savages?
你朝一位中尉開槍了?
Fitzgerald.
菲茨格爾德
21 dead soldiers, more than 40 dead feather necks...
他們死了21個戰士 超過40頭動物
... but you and your boy are the only ones to get walk out alive.
但是你和你兒子卻平安無事
It was kind of a miracle, don't you think?
這真是個奇跡 你不覺得嗎
You need to shut up Fitzgerald.
閉嘴 菲茨格爾德
Is that what you did?
是這樣嗎
Shot one of your own to save this little dog right here?
為了救這個狗崽子 你連自己人都殺
- Shut up. - You want to fight son?
- 閉嘴 - 你想要打架嗎 小子
You were playing with this little boy's momma?
你和他的媽媽搞上了?
- Fitzgerald! - Need to kill her?
- 菲茨格爾德 - 但是你不得不殺了她?
Hey you can quit polishing that rifle,while I'm talking to you.
嘿 我在和你說話呢 別擦槍了
I'm working on it.
我在做事呢
You can work on it later when I'm done talking to you.
等我說完了 你再擦
- Look at me scalp. - That's enough!
- 看著我 低等人 - 夠了
You're forgettin' your place boy.
別蹬鼻子上臉
As far as I can tell my place is right here, on the smart end of this rifle.
就算我蹬鼻子上臉了 現在拿著槍的人可是我
You move along Fitzgerald.
別說了 菲茨格爾德
That's an order.
這是命令
Listen to me.
聽我說
We only have a couple hours of light left.
天就快黑了
We gotta stash these pelts ...
我們要把這些皮毛藏好
... and get rid of the boat, let's go.
然後把船給處理了 快點
Yes, captain.
是 隊長
Beckett.
貝克特
Weston.
韋斯頓
Why are they not jumping?
他們為什麼不跳
It looks like they changed their minds.
看上去他們改變主意了
Smart sons of bitches.
聰明的混蛋
Smart ...
他們很聰明
I ought to be on that boat.
早知道我就不下船了
You did the right thing
你這麼做是對的
Was it the right decision ...
把船留下
... leaving the boat?
是正確的選擇嗎
Ree own that river.
那條河是他們的領地
Would have flanked us.
留在船上就是找死
If we stay east to the ground to those mountains ...
如果我們在山東部活動
... we cut a week of our trip.
我們可以省去一周時間
Land is all dry up there,nothing for the ree to hunt.
那裡地很干 他們會什麼都找不到
- Except us? - Except us.
- 除了我們? - 除了我們
Is it true what Fitzgerald said?
菲茨格爾德說的是真的嗎
Is that why you came out here to the edge of the world?
是因為那樣你才過來這個荒涼之地的嗎
- Glass? - I didn't like the quiet.
- 格拉斯? - 那裡太安靜了
Your boy, he's seen a lot ...
你兒子不該在這
He got a mother you need to get him back to?
他有母親嗎 你能把他送回去嗎
- Glass!? - Hey there are cubs here.
- 格拉斯 - 嘿 這裡有熊崽
Glass!
格拉斯
We got cubs here.
這裡有熊崽
Christ almighty.
我的天啊
Hey you.
嘿 你
Hey!
嘿
He's down here.
他在這裡
- Help me out... - Keep your eyes open, the bear's alive.
- 幫一下我 - 小心點 熊還是活的
Come on, I need your help now.
快點 我需要你的幫忙
Glass.
格拉斯
Oh my god!
我的天啊
- Oh Christ! - Captain.
- 噢 上帝啊 - 隊長
Give me rags now!
把布給我
Push where he bleeds out.
按著流血的地方
Prepare the kit.
把工具准備好
Bridger, you hold that.
布裡傑 拿著這個
- Easy. - Oh god!
- 小心點 - 噢 上帝
Gotta give him credit for taking that grizz down with him.
他能把熊打倒 真不簡單
He shouldn't have fire the shot, the whole
他不該開槍的
place is crawling with fucking tree niggers...
熊聽到後肯定都出來了
Hey that's enough, that's enough!
嘿 夠了 夠了
We're still on ree territory here ...
這裡是土著人的地盤
... this is one of our own men, god dammit.
格拉斯是自己人 媽的
The boy leave him, just got a circle around us.
孩子 你帶兩個人
North and west, take those two with you.
去北邊和東邊看守
Bill, Fryman you take south and east.
比爾 弗裡曼 你們去南邊和西邊
Watch for anyone that might have heard that shot.
小心可能聽到槍聲的人
- Yes sir. - We have to stitch him up.
- 好的 - 我們得給他縫針
What about me?
我呢
It's alright.
沒關系
- You have to... - You stay here.
- 你必須得 - 你留在這
- Hold it down. - I'm sorry Mr. glass. I am so sorry.
- 按著 - 抱歉 格拉斯先生 真的很抱歉
Bridger, hold him. Press down here.
布裡傑 扶著他 按著這裡
He is bleeding down here too.
他這裡也在流血
Torturing the bastard.
那雜種在折磨他
The proper thing to do would be though...Finish him off quick.
如果他不能好轉的話
Unless he has a chance of pulling through.
還不如直接給他個了斷
Pullin' thru? You saw what that grizz did to him.
好轉 你都看見了 他被那只灰熊折磨成了什麼樣子
He'll be dead inside an hour.
他活不過一個小時
Yeah, we all will be if we don't quit waving like that.
如果我們不離開 我們都會是這樣的下場
Towards you and towards that place. I'll hold him. Go.
從你的方向往那邊掰 我抓牢他 掰
Hold him, you go.
穩住了 你快點
Go! Now!
快點 快
- He past out. - Very good.
- 他暈過去了 - 太好了
I'm gonna take advantage and stitch up, let me see.
我正好可以利用這段時間把他的傷口縫起來 讓我看看
Oh god!
哦 天哪
Water.
水
Bridger, go tell the others we'll camp here tonight.
布裡傑 跟他們說我們今晚在這裡扎營
- I'm right here. - Yes, sir.
- 我會陪著你 - 好的
I want everybody up at the crack of dawn.
所有人天亮之前必須起來
Yes sir. Understood cap.
明白 遵命
Carrying Glass would be hard.
帶著格拉斯會很費勁
We need to get ahead as far as possible.
我們得盡可能地走在前面
We'll divide into two groups.
我們要兵分兩路
Fitzgerald, Jones, fryman. You take the east side of the river.
菲茨傑拉德  瓊斯 弗裡曼 你們從河的東邊走
Anderson you scout up front.
安德森 你在前面探路
- That claw don't mourn him. - Everybody else takes turn carrying Glass.
- 弄那爪子又不能哀悼他 - 每個人輪流抬格拉斯
Yes, captain.
遵命 隊長
They're ain't for me.
不是給我的
Do not let him into the water
不要讓他浸到水裡了
get up.
起來
- Fuck off. - That's an order!
- 媽的 - 這是命令
God damn it, don't let him down!
該死 堅持住
Don't let him down.
抬穩了
Watch it.
小心
How are we gonna make it up there?
我們在這兒休息會兒怎麼樣
Slow down a bit.
速度放慢點
It's killing us captain.
我們快堅持不住了 隊長
Lift him Bridger.
抬穩了 布裡傑
Keep it steady ...
穩住
Everybody.
大家加油
And here...
就這兒了
I'm gonna go up and pull...
加油 往上
Here...
抬
Hold it.
穩住
Enough of this shit. We'll never make it across land this way.
真他媽受夠了 照這樣走下去我們根本到不了營地
He is burning out captain.
他不行了 隊長
Captain you ain't doing us nor him...
隊長 如果不是他的話
no favor... going on suffering like this.
我們也不會這麼無助 不會吃這樣的苦頭
Captain!
隊長
Captain, it's all the same up here. We have to go back.
隊長 前面一直都是這樣的地形 看來我們不得不折回去
Find another way.
另辟蹊徑
Hold on.
堅持
Glass...Hugh...
格拉斯 休
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
對不起 對不起
Plant that rag over his eyes Mr. Bridger.
布裡傑先生 用這塊布蒙住他的眼睛
- What? - Sir, I can't.
- 什麼 - 我做不到
Plant that rag over his eyes.
用這塊布蒙住他的眼睛
- What, wait. - Sorry Hugh.
- 什麼 慢著 - 對不起 休
- Wait. Sir, I can't do that. - How do we get back without him?
- 等等 我做不到 - 我們怎麼能不帶他一起回去
- He's the only one who knows the way. - He can't go any further.
- 他是唯一一個認識路的人 - 他熬不過去了
Wave that rag over his eyes. - Wait.
用這塊布蒙住他的眼睛 - 等等
Sir, I can't.
我不能
Wait, you can't ...
不要 你不能
Put a rag over his eyes.
用布蒙住他的眼睛
Lay it over his eyes.
蓋住他的眼睛
Step back.
住手
Stop, Mr. Henry ...
住手 亨利先生
Henry, please.
亨利 求求你
Captain, captain ...
隊長 隊長
Hey, hawk!
嘿 霍克
Calm down kid.
冷靜點孩子
Calm down.
冷靜
Henry, please ...
亨利 求求你
There's a $70 bonus in the rocky mountains fur company
我們還有落基山毛皮公司給的70美元津貼
for two men, who stays ...
可以夠兩個人用 這兩個人
back with glass, to see this through.
得留下來看著格拉斯 一起度過難關
- I'll stay. - Me too.
- 我留下來 - 我也是
Money or not, I'll stay.
不管有沒有好處 我都留下來
I need a third.
我還要一個人
Sorry captain, I have family ...
抱歉隊長 我還有一家老小
I am not crazy.
我可沒瘋
Captain, three men can't hold off a party of ree.
隊長 三個壯漢都不足以對付一幫土著
Much less boys.
更不要說三個小伙子了
Besides, $70 ain't going by nobody lose their ears.
而且70美元肯定是不行的 他們又不是傻子
100 then.
那就100
This man is the only reason we're still alive.
多虧了格拉斯我們才得以活命
Oh captain, we were 45 men when we started, now we're 10, almost 9.
隊長 我們一開始本來有45個人 但現在只剩10個了 還有一個只剩下半條命
He's my father,you can have my share.
他是我父親 你可以把我的那份拿去
Mine too.
我也是
Have our share also.
我們的都給你
Alright.
好
Alright, if Mr. Bridger feels the same way, then I'll lead behind of them.
很好 如果布裡傑先生也是這樣想的的話 我可以在後方領導他們
- You? - Yeah.
- 你 - 是的
You already lost my share of the pelts...
你已經把我的那份毛皮都弄丟了
So I don't got much choice but to try make it up some other means.
所以我除了讓你以其他方式補償我以外 別無選擇
Besides, sticking around for another day or two don't make no difference.
況且 在這兒逗留一兩天一點用都沒有
$300, is to get to go home with something.
300美元 才夠回家
Glass is to be cared for until...
照顧好格拉斯 直到他
Understood?
明白吧
Yeah. You have my word, understand.
嗯 我保證 我知道了
You boys get him down of this slope there somewhere safe before the dark.
你們得在天黑之前把他從這個斜坡抬到安全的地方去
聽著 小伙子們
You heard，the boys.
- Fitzgerald. - Captain.
- 菲茨傑拉德 - 隊長
Glass is to be cared for as long as necessary.
只要格拉斯還活著你們就必須好好照顧他
And a proper burial when it's time. He's earned it.
如果他時候到了 就厚葬他 他配的上
Understand.
明白
$300 goes along way till retiring...
300美元足夠支撐我
Way down to Texas, buy me a decent piece of land...
到德克薩斯 買下一片肥沃的土地
And start pissing in the wind.
然後悠閒度日
Getting the hell out of this godforsaken places.
擺脫這倒霉的破地方
Did ree done that to you?
是那些土著把你害成這樣的嗎
I was just asking.
我只是問問而已
They done it.
是他們
They took their sweet tole with it too
他們還帶著他們心愛的刀具
at the start I didn't feel nothing,
一開始我什麼感覺也沒有
I just heard the sound of...
我只是聽見刀
knife scraping against my skull, you know ...
劃開我的腦門的聲音 你可以想象一下
They were all laughin' and whoopin' and hollerin' what not...
他們全都笑著 鬧著 大聲喊著
Then the blood came ...
然後血就湧出來了
The cold started streaming down my face and my eyes ...
就像一股寒流 一發不可收拾地流過我的臉頰 我的眼睛
The breathing it in...
然後流進我的喉嚨
Choking on it.
堵住了我的呼吸
That's when I felt it.
這個時候我才真切地感覺到了痛苦
I felt all of it.
我完完全全地感受到了它
They got my head turned inside out.
他們把我的頭皮翻了過來
Jesus.
天啊
Yeah, them Indians down Texas way ...
是啊 印第安人侵入德克薩斯
they may rob you, ain't gonna take your topknot.
他們會搶劫你的錢財 但不會把你變成禿頭
When was it?
什麼時候的事
God damn, will you just, would you quit that noise now, will ya?
媽的 你能別再發出這種聲音嗎
Or just ...Leave it.
或者干脆別弄了
I'm following further back from heading against
我一開始反對帶著你 後來還是妥協了
the boys on account of tending to you.
就因為那幾個家伙都在維護你
We got to get up that damn mountain but the wind keeps chasing us down.
我們得在刮大風之前翻過那座該死的大山
If you're ready ...
如果你准備好了
take the sacrament.
去見上帝的話
I can do that for you.
我可以幫你一把
What you holding to, Glass?
你在堅持什麼 格拉斯
You know?
你知道嗎
Would be better...
如果你現在
If you would've take that last breath of yours now.
已經咽下最後一口氣的話 對我們來說
For all of us.
這會是一件好事
You hung tough.
而你還在硬撐著
That's something.
我要拜托你
一件事情 格拉斯
I'm begging you， Glass.
Them ree, they are so close now i can smell them ...
那群土著 他們就快逼近了 我能感覺到
and I know you can smell them, too. When you got to think.
而且我相信你也感覺到了 如果你在想什麼的話
You gotta think of your boy.
你想想你的兒子
Alright? Cause you're gonna kill him.
行嗎 因為你會害死他的
You'll kill all of us.
你會害死我們所有人的
I can muzzle you if you like.
你想的話我可以替你了結
Take away the suffering,really quick and easy ...
干淨利落地帶走你的痛苦
... no one has to know that you give up.I do that.
沒有人會知道是你自己放棄的
All you gotta to do is blink ...
你所要做的就是眨一下眼睛
... if you want me to do that.
如果你想讓我這麼干的話
Save your boy and blink.
眨一下眼睛就可以救那孩子一命
You just have to blink.
只要眨一下眼睛就行
Yeah.
行了
Oh yes!
足夠了
You best hope that the good lord get his ass here quick, huh.
但願上帝盡快降臨到你身上吧
Maybe he'll forgive your sins, you know maybe he won't ...
或許他會原諒你的罪 或許不會
You just sudden commend it to the lord.
但總之你就到了他的身旁
Through Jesus Christ, the lord of all reality and mercy ...
奉主耶穌基督的名 全能和仁慈的主
Get away. Get away.
滾開 滾開
You ok? Jim. Jim ... help.
你沒事吧 吉姆 吉姆 救命
- Help.- Calm down. Alright, you don't understand.
- 救命 - 冷靜 行嗎 你不明白
Don't shout, you'll get us all fuckin' killed.
別開槍 你會害死我們的
Keep away.
離我遠點
I'll tell Jim and the captain what you did and they'll hang you.
我要告訴吉姆和船長你做的好事 他們會判你絞刑
- You have to understand this ...- They'll hang you ...
- 你必須搞明白 - 你會被吊死的
Jim help.Jim get over here.
吉姆救命 吉姆快點過來
Keep quiet!!
小點聲
Shit.
該死
Got one beaver half.
弄到半只海狸
His breathing changed?
他還活著嗎
I ain't noticed.
我沒留意
Damn, he's cold as ice.
天哪 他冷得像塊冰
Here Mr. glass ... this will help ...
抬起頭 格拉斯先生 這個很有用
It will keep you warm.
它可以幫你御寒
It's alright.
沒事了
Where is hawk?
霍克去哪兒了
He ain't with you?
他沒和你在一起
- No.- No?
- 沒啊 - 沒嗎
I understand Mr. glass.
我知道 格拉斯先生
Alright.
好了
I think I'm gonna get a fire going.
我去生堆篝火
Yeah, sounds like a good idea.
行 是個好主意
Hawk!
霍克
You killed my son.
你殺死了我的孩子
Hawk!
霍克
Bridge, there's about 20 of them down by the creek.
布裡傑 從小溪邊來了大概20個人
They're headed this way.
他們朝我們這裡來了
Now grab your shit and let's go.
現在帶上你東西趕緊走
Shit. Wait. What do we do?
我去 等等 我們要干什麼
Run right now.
逃跑啊
- What about hawk? - He ain't our problem no more.
- 那霍克怎麼辦 - 他不重要
We can't just leave him here.
我們不能留他一個在這兒
He's going to be scalped.
他會被剝皮的
If that ree can find us, can't he?
除非土著能找到我們 他能嗎
Wait. What about glass?
等等 那格拉斯呢
He ain't our problem no more, he is like us, he's on his own.
他也不再是我們的問題了 我們現在都一樣 都要靠自己生存了
No, no, we made a promise to captain ...
不 不行 我們向船長保證過
I'll give him a proper burial when the time is needed.
當時機來臨時我會給他個體面的葬禮
wait he needs that rifle.
他需要那把步槍
He can't do nothing with it if you tarred it to his hands.
即使把槍擱在他手裡他也無法扣動扳機
Now come on get your shit. Let's go.
趕快帶上你的東西 我們快跑
No, no, we can't do this.
不 不可以 我們不能這麼干
- We got no fucking choice. - We can't. Look at him.
- 我們他媽的沒得選擇了 - 不可以 你看他
- Alright, shitting brain ... - What you doin?
- 好吧 傻瓜 - 你在干嗎
Can you take him? Come on.
你能抬起他嗎 快點
No, no wait...
不 等下
Easy, slowly Fitz ...
慢點 輕點啊菲茨
Easy.
慢點
- I can't ... - Damn ...
- 我做不到 - 靠
Shit, get this shit.
靠 抬起來
Wait, hold ...
等下
- Hold on!
慢一些
Shut up.
閉嘴
Hold on.
慢一些
Fitz...
菲茲
- What are you doing? - What it looks like I'm doing?
- 你在干什麼 - 你覺得我在干什麼
A proper burial.
一個體面的葬禮
Like he wanted.
就像他希望的那樣
- No, not like this. - Why not?
- 不 不是這樣的 - 為什麼不是呢
He is alive Fitz.He's alive.
他還活著 菲茲 活著沒死
So shoot him.
那就開槍殺死他
I have to go, I have to...
我得跑了 我必須離開了
I'm sorry.
對不起
Captain, this way ...
隊長 走這裡
There's a path down here.
那兒有條路通下來
There's no way through down here.
這裡無路可走
There ain't shit down there,we go climb over.
這裡啥都沒有 我們要爬過去
Cross can go to hell.
爬個鬼啊
- What does the map say? - Keep climbing.
- 地圖上怎麼說的 - 接著爬
We climb captain.
我們爬過去 隊長
We keep climbing.
我們要一直爬
Until we reach our gate.
直到到達出口那
Climb.
一直爬
- You got away from Murph? - Yeah.
- 你不跟著墨菲了 - 是的
You wait for it.
你等一下
Captain.
隊長
Sir. Murphy says there's a way down there.
兄弟 墨菲說前面有一條路可以下去
Who we following?
我們到底跟誰走
You follow who you want.
你想跟誰就跟誰
I'm going up.
反正我往上走了
We all need to be going up.Blair, come here!
我們都必須上來 快過來 布萊爾
Fire's done.
篝火派對結束了
I can't still feel my feet ...
我的雙腳都失去知覺了
Besides, didn't we put enough distance between us and them ree anyhow?
再說了 我們不是已經和土著拉開很遠的距離了嗎
Well...
這個嘛
...a dozen ree could still made twice the good time as we can.
12個土著行進起來要比我們快上一倍
- 20.- What?
- 二十 - 什麼
I thought you said that you saw 20 ree before.
我以為你之前說的是二十土著
Yeah, what you talking about?
是啊 怎麼了
You woke me up?
你叫醒我
You said you saw 20 ree down by the creek.
說你看到20個土著從小溪那邊過來
Well yeah, 20 or dozen, it don't matter ...
對啊 二十或者十二 這並不重要
...i wasn't gonna exactly hang around the creek
我又沒打算在一邊小溪邊走來走去
... counting fuckin' feathers, now would I?
數著他們到底有多少人 我現在也不會數
Matter a fact.
事實很重要
What was you doing down by the creek all by yourself?
你一個人到底在小溪邊干什麼
I thought I already brought up plenty of water.
我覺得我已經打了足夠多的水了
Hey!
說你呢
Answer me Fitzgerald, i asked you a question.
回答我 菲茨傑拉德 我在問你問題
Don't go questioning me now on the account of fact that we all feel ...
因為撇下格拉斯而感覺內疚之後
... guilty about leaving this glass behind.
就不要再過來質疑我
Answer me or I'm gonna blow your head off.
你不回答 我就爆掉你的頭
You got a short memory boy.
你可真是記不住事兒 孩子
Your ass is still be floatin around Missouri right now...
要不是我
... if it wasn't for me.
你的屍體早已被丟在密蘇裡河了
Now wanna ask questions ...
現在你又要問我問題
... what you want ask if you won't know asking.
你什麼都不知道憑什麼來質疑我
You want to know why you left mr.Glass back there for dead, hah?
你想知道你為什麼扔下格拉斯在那兒等死嗎
Maybe...
或許
...while you left your little boy friend wandering around, you
當你扔下你的小男朋友的時候
don't know if he's still alive yet. That what you want to know?
他生死未卜 你是想知道這個嗎
I'll tell you lies 'cause you ain't a man yet.
我對你說謊因為你是個小孩
Alright? Because you were scared shitless
行了吧 因為你都嚇得不行了
... and you're scared now.Now put your rifle down.
你現在也是  快放下槍
- The ree. - What off it?
- 那些土著 - 關他們什麼事
Tell me right now and be honest.Did you see 'em?
老實告訴我 你到底有沒有看到土著
- Put your rifle down.- Did you see the ree?
- 放下你的槍 - 到底看見土著沒
No.
沒有
Not a single one.
影子都沒看見一個
You fucking lie to me?
你他媽的騙我
You lie to me!
你騙我
I had to scare samo sense into you boy.
我必須讓你感到害怕
Now glass was dead, hawk we don't know about ...
現在格拉斯死了 霍克不知所蹤
There is no point either of us
dying here ... do you understand?
沒有必要再多一具屍體了 你明白嗎
The way I see it, I saved your life twice now son .
就我所見 我救了你兩次 孩子
I ought to be god to you ...
我是你的恩人
And god giveth, god taketh away.
我能給你 就也都能收回來
Shit.
我去
Fuck.
他媽的
Next time, if you want to shoot somebody ...
下次 你想開槍殺人
...you might wanna use, you might wanna use powder.
你最好先把火藥
...prime your rifle.
裝到你的槍裡去
Come on...
快點
...let's get up. Grab your shit.
趕緊起來 帶上你的東西
Captain wait...
隊長 等等
- Who did this? - I don't know.
- 這是誰干的 - 我不知道
Could be captain Leavenworth boys.
可能是萊文沃斯隊長的人干的
Hm, yeah.
也是
You put some eyes on the back of your head.
提高警惕 注意四周
These Indians ain't never as dead as you'll think they are.
這些印第安人絕不會像你想那樣都死光了的
Look at them, they're always stinking of shit.
瞧瞧他們 總是臭得要死
We got horses over here.
我看到那裡有幾匹馬
Alright, bridger.
快點 布裡傑
We got horses.
我們有馬騎了
What you wanna do about this pigs?
你想拿這些豬怎麼辦
You alright there kid?
你還好嗎 孩子
You're head in the right place?
你沒有心不在焉吧
I guess.
我想是的
Can't help thinking about
whether we did the right...
我忍不住想我們到底做得對不對
No.
別
Ain't our place to wonder.
這不是該想的事情
Good lord's got us on the road, whether we chose or not.
上帝與我們同在 無論我們做出何種選擇
My pa being one ...Wasn't a religious man you, you know?
我父親並不是一個虔誠的人 你懂嗎
If you couldn't grow it,or kill it or eat it ...
如果你不能從中成長 消化或是消滅掉它
... then he just plain all didn't believe in it and that was it.
他就一味地不信 就這樣了
And this one time he hit on up the old saber hills.
有一次他去老劍山打獵
San saber hills ...
就是聖劍山
Joined up with a couple of texan range buddies of his to hunt, you know.
一起去打獵的還有一些德克薩斯兄弟們
Pretty routine, you know, they done it like hundred times before.
這本是一個好線路 你知道的 他們已經干過幾百次了
Should have been three days of kill, but on Saturday, well it all went fucked.
本應該是三天的打獵 但到星期六 厄運就來了
Somehow that night he has to lose buddies ...
不知怎的那晚死了弟兄
... and on top of it all ...
幾乎損失殆盡
... the comanches they went and took the horses, so ...
科曼奇人搶走了他們的馬匹
...he was starving,
他太餓了
delirious...
神志昏迷
... and crawles up into this mud ...
爬進了這片泥地
... like the group of trees out there in the middle of nowhere ...
就像一棵樹立在一片陌生空曠的大地上
... just sticking up in this ocean of scrub ...
附著在一片灌木叢上
... and he found religion.
就是此刻他找到了信仰
At that moment...
那時
...he told me...
他告訴我
... he found god.
他看見了上帝
It turns out ...
結果是
...the god ...
上帝
... he is a squirrel.
是一只松鼠
Yeah. They go meet him one...
是的 他們遇到了一個 上帝
I found god, he used to say.
他經常說 我發現了上帝
Who has sitting and basking ...
上帝就那麼懶洋洋地
... in glory in subliminal mercy ...
沐浴在聖光和悲憫之中
I shot knee that son of a bitch ...
我給那兔崽子的膝蓋來了一槍
Yeah, you might wanna close your eyes kid.
小子 你最好合眼休息一下吧
A grizzly.
一只灰熊
Yeah!
瞧
There she is.
我們到了
We did it.
我們做到了
You ought to be proud of yourself boy.
小子 你應該感到自豪才是
Yeah.
是啊
Well we followed orders ... we just skipped the funeral part.
我們嚴格執行命令 就差沒開個追悼會了
Don't go down there start going no kind of conscience, alright?
下去之後別良心發現亂說話 明白嗎
Cause sure it's not an outcome that us both swinging from couple grants.
我可不想讓咱們的獎賞竹籃打水一場空
Now, we did what we had to do.
咱們也是迫不得已
We had the extra day, so we managed to dig a little deeper ...
時間挺寬裕的 所以我們想法兒把坑挖得深了點兒
leave some rocks on top, so that the scavengers couldn't get out to him...
在上頭蓋了些石頭 那些野人就沒法挖墳兒了
we was done right and all.
我們把一切都打理妥當了
He was buried right.
他被體面地厚葬了
- Sir ... - The truth is that, ah ...
- 先生 - 事實上 呃
When hawk disappeared, i was worried about the savages.
霍克失蹤的時候 我擔心是野人干的
I was ready to get..Moving on out you know, but...
你要知道 我當時准備 開溜了 但是
Bridger here, he argued to stay.
布裡傑他堅持留下
He argued to stay so that ...
他堅持要留下
... he could at least build the cross, or something ...
至少讓他扎個十字架 或者其他什麼東西
to put on top of glass's grave, and that's what he did...
好放在格拉斯的墳頭兒上 他做到了
That's what we did.
我們一起做到了
Glad to hear you pulled your weight Mr. bridger.
布裡傑先生 很高興你做好了分內之事
I know you would.
我一直對你深信不疑
Yeah, well, more important weight than captain decides
喔 他干的可比隊長吩咐的多多了
...this man here, he is my partner.
這個家伙 他是我生死相依的同伴
Alright
好吧
Am I to assume that there was agreed arrangement did not changed?
之前說好的酬勞標准沒變吧
Fortunately, for me it did not, no.
幸運的是 我的要求沒變
Thank you.
那可謝謝你了
For your courage, honor ..
因你的勇氣 榮耀
- ... and service. - Yeah...
- 和奉獻 - 恩
Deal or no deal Mr. bridger, you deserve something for what you did.
布裡傑先生 不管之前什麼酬勞標准 你的作為值得嘉賞
Thank you.
非常感謝你
Kid's been beating himself up all the bad round trip.
那孩子已經自責一路了
We all saw the shape glass was in, it was no more to be done, right?
大家都清楚格拉斯的狀況  我們已無力回天 不是嗎
Yeah.
是啊
We all saw it.
大家都心知肚明
Don't make a sound.
別出聲
Be quiet.
安靜點兒
- May I join you? - Yes.
- 加我一個行嗎 - 當然
- Yeah? - Yes.
- 真的嗎 - 你自便
Damn I was wondering when we might be getting paid for that haul?
他媽的 我一直在想我們什麼時候能拿到那批毛皮貨的報酬
Cause those pelts we collect, they are still out there ...
我們收集的那堆毛皮 它們還在原地兒
... they're covered with dirt and some snow,
在灰塵和雪底下壓著
but they are there, and that ain't my fault.
至少貨沒丟 天公不作美可不是我們的責任
I'm waiting for captain Leavenworth to arrive with his army ...
我在等萊文沃思隊長率領著他的隊伍回來
And then we'll have enough men...
屆時我們就有足夠的人手
to get back out there and shoot some civilization ...
回去給那些該死的阿裡卡拉人一個血的教訓
... into those fucking arikara, get back our pelts.
然後把我們的毛皮搶回來
Alright, alright.
好吧 好吧
And now when is that supposed to happen?
你這白日夢什麼時候成真呢
I don't know but...
我不知道 但是...
... until then nobody gets paid.
那之前 誰也拿不到錢
Listen here, alright?
聽著 成嗎
I was hired to trap them...I wasn't hired to guard them.
我是給獵物下套的 不是走鏢的
The way I see it ... you got a safe.
依我之見 你賺回了本錢
- Probably full of money. - You signed a contract.
- 說不准盆滿缽盈 - 你簽過合同
To protect your boss and your boss's property.
保護頭兒和他的貨
And that safe isn't full anymore, it's short about $300.
而且我已經賠了300塊了
Short? Short? What the hell is that supposed to mean?
賠錢 什麼賠錢 你他媽什麼意思
It means according to my cash records...
意思就是 我的財政記錄顯示
You purchased more goods on the expedition than what you are owed by the company.
公司欠你的酬勞可比你公費出差的花銷少得多
happy new year, Fitzgerald.
新年快樂  菲茨傑拉德
white man at the gate.
門口有個白人
What's up? Who you are?
出了什麼事兒 你是誰
I have no weapon, I have no weapons.
我沒帶武器 我沒帶武器
- Dobb, get the captain. - I have no weapon....
- 多布 把隊長叫來 - 我沒帶武器
Where are your men?
你的手下呢
- Dead, they all dead. - Who were they?
- 死了 他們都死了 - 他們是誰
I don't know, something to eat please.
我什麼都不知道 求你給口飯吃吧
Food comes at price.
想吃飯就得給錢
I have no money.
我身無分文
Then you don't eat this, see how that works.
那你就沒飯吃 懂了吧
Maybe you can give back some of the stolen pelts you buy from the Indians.
你可以分給我們點兒 你從印第安人那兒買來的被盜的毛皮貨
- Not now Jones. - Silver...
- 不是說這個的時候 瓊斯 - 銀幣
This is silver.
這是銀幣
Oh yeah?
哦 是嗎
This all you got?
你就這點兒
There was 9 ... but my friend he died in the snow...
我們本來有9個人 可是我的朋友死在了冰天雪地裡
... and the others were ...
其他人
... by wolves ... by wolves ...
被狼 被狼
Wait where did you get this?
等等 你從哪兒拿到的這個
The canteen.
這個水壺
He ... he drop it in the snow.
他 他把水壺丟在了雪地裡
- Who, who? - I do not know, I don't see. I don't see.
- 誰丟的 誰 - 我不知道 我沒看見 沒看見
It could be hawk.
有可能是霍克
Yeah, it could be.
嗯 有可能
- Maybe it was Weston - How far from here?
- 有可能是韋斯特 - 離這兒有多遠
- How far from here? - 13 miles ...
- 離這兒到底有多遠 -13公裡
Northwest ... near the yellowstone.
西北方向 .靠近黃石地區
Get the horses saddled.
備好馬匹
Torches and supplies, $10 a men.
帶上火把和糧草 每人10美元獎賞
- Anderson, you stay here. - Yes sir.
- 安德森你留下看家 - 遵命長官
Feed him and watch him ...
喂飽之後監視他
I'll get you a drink.
我給你拿點兒酒來
Open the gate.
打開大門
Keep your guard up.
時刻保持警惕
Eyes in front.
緊盯前方
Slow.
慢著
Who you are?
前方何人
Beckett? Is that you?
貝克特 是你嗎
Weston?
是韋斯頓嗎
Glass.
格拉斯
- That's glass... - Glass...
- 是格拉斯 - 格拉斯...
It's okay.
沒事了
Jesus Christ.
老天呀
Jesus Christ, what happened?
天哪 發生了什麼
Where is he?
他在哪兒
Johns take him, go.
約翰斯 快帶他走
Go, I'm riding ahead.
快走 我騎在前面
Phil. Take Bridger.
菲爾 抓住布裡傑
Take Bridger.
給我抓住布裡傑
- You got it Glass. - Go.
- 你能行的格拉斯 - 走
Open the gate.
打開大門
- Have you seen Fitzgerald? - No sir.
- 看到菲茨傑拉德了嗎 - 沒有 先生
Get up.
起來
都起來
- Have you seen Fitzgerald? - No sir.
- 看到菲茨傑拉德了嗎 - 沒有 先生
Fitzgerald.
菲茨傑拉德
- Oh easy. - Where did he go?
- 哦 冷靜 - 他去哪兒了
- Who? - Fitzgerald.
- 誰 -菲茨傑拉德
Where did he go?
他逃到哪兒去了
- I have no idea. - Tell me or I'll take your head off.
- 我不知道 - 告訴我 否則我一搶崩掉你的腦袋
- Captain, I swear to god. - Tell me!
- 隊長 我對天起誓 - 快告訴我
- Tell me! - Texas.
- 你他媽的快說 - 德州
- Texas? - He said he was going to Texas.
- 你確定 - 他說他要去德州
I swear to god, he said he was going to re-enlist.
我發誓 他說他要再服一次軍役
And he start talking of a property, a decent piece of land ...
然後他談起了房子 一塊上好的地...
... he's heading to Texas. I swear to god.
他出發去了德州 我發誓
Stay here.
待在這兒別動
Fitzgerald.
菲茨傑拉德
God dammit.
該死的
Open the gate.
打開大門
Open her up.
快開門
Search captain.
快去找隊長
Get him to the doctor, now.
送他去看醫生 現在就去
You said he was dead.
你說他死了
- You said he was dead. - I thought he was dead, I swear.
- 你騙我說他死了 - 我以為他死了 我發誓
- You're a liar. - He lied to me.
- 你個騙子 - 是菲茨傑拉德騙了我
Liar, you left. You left him out there.
騙子 你拋棄了他 你就把他丟在荒郊野外
- I thought he was ... - Say the lord's prayer.
- 我以為他 - 做死前禱告吧
- What? - Say the lord's prayer.
-什麼 - 你他媽的趕緊祈禱
Our father...
在天堂的
... who are in heaven ... I can't ...
上帝啊我不能
Shut up.
閉嘴
Shut up! From here on you are a prisoner charged with treason.
閉嘴 從現在起 你就是個負著背叛之名的囚犯
Take him to the cage. Take him to the cage!
把他關起來 把他給我關起來
You handle or I'll shoot him!
把他關起來否則我一槍打死他
I thought he was gonna die...
我以為他命不久矣了
Get up
站起來
I could help, please.
求你了 我能幫得上忙
Please captain ...
求你了 隊長
Alright. Come on.
好了 快來
1, 2, 3.
一 二 三
Slide, slide. Slide.
拖 拖 拖
- How is he? - He'll be fine, but there is swelling ...
- 他傷勢如何 - 沒什麼大礙 就是傷口有點紅腫...
...needs to rest.
需要安心休養
I'll be back to check up on him.
我過會兒再來檢查
He ran off, didn't he?
他落荒而逃了 是不是
Bridger is telling the truth ...
布裡傑所說屬實
- How is that? - Fitzgerald lied to him...
- 怎麼回事 - 菲茨傑拉德騙了他
... he was just following orders.
他只是按命令辦事兒
He wasn't there when Fitzgerald stabbed my boy to death.
菲茨傑拉德的匕首刺進我兒子心髒時 他並不在場
Is that what happened? He killed hawk?
這就是事情的原委嗎 他殺了霍克
I need a horse and a gun.
我需要一匹馬 一把槍
No, you need to rest and something to eat.
不行 你需要好好進食調養
- I'm going after him. - No.
- 我要去追他 - 不
You'll never find him without me.
不帶上我 你永遠也找不到他
If we wait till morning he'll have a days head start and he get away.
若是等到早上再動身 他早就逃之夭夭了
No he won't.
他無處可逃
He's afraid.
他浸淫在恐懼之中
He knows how far I came for him.
他深知我追捕了他多久
Same as that elk, when they get afraid they run deep in to the woods ...
猶如麋鹿 一旦感到畏怯 就慌不擇路闖進密林深處
I got him trapped, he just...
我設陷阱套住它 它只是
- He doesn't know it yet. - How can you be so sure?
- 它還毫不自知 - 你怎麼能有十足的把握
Cause he got everything to lose.
因為他已經一無所有
All I had was that boy ...
我兒子曾是我的全部
... and he took him from me.
而他殘忍的奪走了他的性命
I can't let you go back out there.
我不能放任你去雪原
- Not again. - No.
- 我不想重蹈覆轍 - 不
I ain't afraid to die anymore.
我已不再畏懼死亡
I've done that already.
我已經死了
I'm going with you.
我跟你一起去
這是他的馬留下的 對吧 喔是的
It's his horse, alright？Yeah.
No way he could have ridden through the night.
他不可能馬不停蹄地騎了一夜
How far ahead?
我們落後多少
- Half a day at the most. - Could be ree.
- 最多半天的路程 - 有可能是土著留下的
If they aren't his, we lose him.
如果這不是他留下的 那我們就完全失去線索了
He must get re-enlisted so he can justify killing again.
為了合法殺人 他必須得重新服役
This tracks right here are his.
這些一定是他留下的蹤跡
Come on.
走吧
I can't remember my wife's face.
我記不起我妻子的臉了
Last week she was still with me.
上周她還跟我在一塊兒
Now she's gone.
現在她卻不在我身邊
I worry I won't recognize her when I get back home.
我擔心等我回去的時候 已經認不得她了
Is it true you killed an officer?
你真的殺了一個軍官嗎
I just killed a man who was trying to kill my son.
我只是殺了一個企圖殺掉我兒子的人
- Smoke. - How close?
- 有煙 - 還有多遠
No more than a mile up that way.
往那邊走個一公裡左右
I'm gonna head up to the west you go down to the east ...
我往西行 你往東走
- See if we can find some tracks. - What if it's the ree?
- 看看能不能找到些線索 - 如果是土著呢
If it's the ree, you turn right back around and meet me back here.
若是土著 你即刻折回來 和我碰頭
Hey!
嘿
I wouldn't expect to find a man of your statue ...
沒想到你這種身份的人
... so far away from his stove when ...
在這天寒地凍的早上 竟然不圍著爐子取暖
... the morning is so cold as this. Captain, are you lost?
你這是迷路了嗎 隊長
I'm here to take you back to fort kahowa.
我是來捉你回凱何華營地的
Where you will be trialed for murder.
你將會以殺人罪被審判
Yes sir?
是嗎先生
I ain't crazy about your plan.
我對你的計劃可沒什麼興趣
Beside, I got one of my own.
再說了 我自有盤算
We had a deal glass.
我們說好了的 格拉斯
I tried to tell your boy, alright?
我試圖跟你兒子解釋 懂嗎
I tried to tell him what was happening, but he won't listen ...
我試著跟他解釋清楚 但是他根本不聽....
And he kept on screaming. And he was gonna get everybody killed.
他瘋了似的大喊大叫 想害死我們所有人
You and me...
你和我
... we had a deal.
我們協商好了的
We all know what happened out there.
究竟發生了什麼 你我心照不宣
And on my soul to lord
向主賭上我的靈魂
lord he knows what happened out there.
天可明鑒 到底發生了什麼
There was no deal.
我們從來沒有過協議
You killed my boy.
你殺了我兒子
Maybe you should have raised a man ...
你應該培養個男子漢
... instead of a some girly little bitch.
而不是個娘們似的小婊子
God dammit!
該死的
You came all this way just for your revenge?
你千裡迢迢來這 就是為了復仇嗎
Well you enjoy it glass.
好好享受復仇的快感吧 格拉斯
Cause there ain't nothing gonna bring your boy back.
這世上什麼也不能讓你兒子死而復生